pgbrandsampler.com 2011-10-06

# Procter & Gamble Privacy Notice

Information We Collect                                                                                                                                                                                                                      Click here for more information 

  * We collect information about you from a variety of sources, including:

  * Information we collect from you directly.
  * Information we collect about you when you visit our site, use our services, or view our online advertisements.
  * Information we collect about you from other sources, such as commercially available sources.

  * All the information we collect about you may be combined to help us tailor our communications to you and to develop world-class products and services.

Uses / Information Sharing                                                                                                                                                                                                           Click here for more information 

  * We use the information we collect to provide the products and services you request, to tell you about other products and services offered by P&G, and to manage our sites and services.
  * In general, we do not share your personal information with third-party marketers, unless we have asked for and obtained your explicit consent. 
  * We may share your information: 

  * With our third-party service suppliers, including those who work on behalf of P&G and our business partners to send you joint communications that we hope you find of interest.
  * If a P&G brand is sold to another company.
  * To protect and defend the right and property of P&G (including enforcing our Terms and Conditions).
  * When required by law, and / or public authorities.

Your Choices                                                                                                             Click here for more information 

  * We give you choices about how we communicate with you.   

  * You can stop receiving promotional email or postal communications from a particular P&G brand or program through this Privacy Notice. Please [click here](http://www.pg.com/privacy/contact_us/contact_us/privacy-central-contact-interactive.html) to select your country and learn how to complete your request.  

  * We take steps to keep your personal information accurate. You can view, correct, or update the contact information you provide P&G.   

  * [Click here](http://www.pg.com/privacy/contact_us/contact_us/privacy-central-contact-interactive.html) to select your country and learn how to access and update the contact information you provided P&G. 

Important Information

  * P&G is committed to working with consumers to obtain a fair resolution of any complaint or concern about privacy.
  * P&G complies with country data protection laws.
  * We cooperate with country data protection authorities if they believe a privacy problem has occurred.
  * We participate in the US Council of [Better Business Bureau's (BBB)](https://www.bbb.org/online/consumer/cks.aspx?ID=292000103) Accredited Business Program and BBB EU Safe Harbor Dispute Resolution.

| 

How to Contact Us

  * To contact us with a question [click here](http://www.pg.com/privacy/contact_us/contact_us/privacy-central-contact-interactive.html) (for country specific addresses)

  * Or write to us at:  
P&G Global Privacy Team  
PO Box 599  
Cincinnati, OH 45202   
USA

  * To read our full Consumer Privacy Statement click here.
  * To read our Global Privacy Policy [click here.](http://www.pg.com/en_US/sustainability/point_of_view/privacy.shtml)
  * Click here  to view Answers to Frequently Asked Questions
